const questions = [
    {
        question: '  1- What is SMS phishing, also known as smishing?',
        options: ['Sending fake SMS messages to get personal information from recipients', ' Receiving premium SMS messages at no extra cost', ' Sending promotional SMS messages from legitimate companies'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: '  2- Voice phishing, or vishing, is characterized by:',
        options: ['Regular check-up calls from healthcare providers ', 'Legitimate phone calls from banks to verify account details', 'Fraudulent phone calls to extract personal information from individuals'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: '  3- What is the primary goal of a whaling attack?', 
        options: ['To install malware on as many computers as possible within an organization', 'To deceive high-ranking officials into transferring sensitive data information', ' To gain unauthorized access to the physical premises of a company'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: '  4- Which of the following is an internet scam done by cyber-criminals where the user is convinced digitally to provide confidential information: ',
        options: [' MiTM attack', 'Phishing attack ', 'DoS attack '],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: '  5- You get a text message from a vendor who asks you to click on a link to renew your password so that you can log in to its website. You should:',
        options: ['Pick up the phone and call the vendor, using a phone number you know to be correct, to confirm that the request is real. ', 'Reply to the text to confirm that you really need to renew your password.  ', ' Click on the link. If it takes you to the vendor’s website, then you’ll know it’s not a scam '],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: '  6- What happens if you click on a phishing SMS link or attachment?',
        options: ['Browser/app is closed without any prompt.  ', 'You are redirected to a website that asks you to enter sensitive information or directs you to download an attachment. ', 'None of the above  '],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: '  7- What is the best way to prevent phishing from being successful?',
        options: [' Don not let children or teens go online. ', 'Send an email back with false information.', 'Educate people about phishing.  '],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: '  8-  _____________ refers to phishing performed over smart-phone by calling.',
        options: [' Algo-based phishing ', ' Email-based phishing ', ' Vishing  '],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: '  9-  ____________ or smishing is one of the simplest types of phishing where the target victims may get a fake order detail with a cancellation link.',
        options: ['Algo-based phishing', ' SMS phishing ', ' Domain Phishing '],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: '  10- What does the term “phishing” refer to in cybersecurity?',
        options: ['social engineering technique to gain unauthorized access to a network.  ', ' type of malware that spreads through email attachments.  ', 'technique to detect vulnerabilities in a system. '],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: '  11- What is data security?',
        options: ['A policy that determines who can use the internet.', ' A tool used to analyze data.  ', '  The practice of protecting digital information from unauthorized access, corruption, or theft.'],
        answer: 2
    }
];

